https://www.layyous.com/en/website-related/privacy-statement/2-122

HomeAssisted ReproductionThe use of PRP (Platelets Rich Plasma) to increase success rate in IVFAssisted Reproductive Technology (ART)In Vitro Fertilization - I.V.FIntracytoplasmic Sperm Injection - ICSIIVF Related Procedures - Cryopreservation - Ovarian hyper stimulation syndrome - OHSSIntra Uterine Insemination - IUI IVF Success Rates - IUI Success RatesIVF And ICSI Videos - Procedure And Process Involved IVF and ICSI PhotosIntracytoplasmic morphologically selected sperm Injection IMSIEmbryo glueAssisted HatchingEmbryo Blastocyst CultureIVF Failure - Treating Failed In Vitro FertilizationPreimplantation Genetic DiagnosisIn Vitro Fertilization Patients Frequently Asked QuestionsFertilized Oocytes and Embryos PhotosIVF Laboratory TourOocytes and Sperms PhotosPhysiological Selection of sperm for ICSI (PICSI)Microsurgical Sperm Retrieval from the Testicle (Micro-TESE)The ART of In vitro Fertilization How to increase fertility for Men And Women for natural concepton and IVFSex selection Before PregnancyInfertilityInfertility GuideFertilization - Fertility PotentialCauses of Infertility in WomenCauses of Infertility in MenDiagnosis Of Infertility In WomenDiagnosis of Infertility In MenTreatment of infertilityHow to increase fertility for Men And Women for natural concepton and IVF Facts About Smoking and FertilityVaricocele Effect on Infertility and its Management Natural Fertility Boosters Herbal supplements For InfertilityPelvic Adhesions And InfertilityStress and InfertilityPolycystic Ovarian Syndrome - PCOSPCO Patients FAQPresent and futuristic developments in fertility treatmentInfertility Frequently Asked QuestionsFrequently Asked QuestionsWeird Factors That Could Affect Your FertilitySleep Correlation with Male InfertilityMale Hypogonadotropic hypogonadismGenetic causes of male infertilityOvarian CystsSex selection Before Pregnancy PregnancyPregnancy GuidePregnancy Month by MonthPregnancy Month by MonthFirst Month Pregnancy - 1 month pregnantSecond Month Pregnancy - 2 months pregnantThird Month Pregnancy - 3 months pregnantFourth-month-pregnancy - 4 months pregnantFifth Month Pregnancy - 5 months pregnantSixth Month Pregnancy - 6 months pregnantSeventh Month Pregnancy - 7 months pregnantEighth Month Pregnancy - 8 months pregnantNinth Month Pregnancy - 9 months pregnantAdvice for Pregnant Women - Tips For Pregnant WomenHeartburn during pregnancySex selection Before PregnancyGestational Diabetes (Diabetes During Pregnancy)Cerebral Palsy Causes Classification and TreatmentCord blood,Umbilical Cord blood CollectionEctopic PregnancyContraception - Different Birth ControlsPiles - Haemorrhoids in PregnancyCauses of Recurrent MiscarriageConstipation During PregnancySex during pregnancyAnemia in pregnancyPregnancy ExercisesPregnancy After 35Pregnancy Video clips7 Most Common Toxins During Pregnancy that Affect your Childs Health and
How To Avoid ThemAnterior Placenta During Pregnancy - Everything You Need to KnowOral Health Care During Pregnancy
| Dr N LayyousPost Pregnancy DietMolar Pregnancy5 Tasty breakfast recipes that will quash your pregnancy blues detectable cravings every dayPreterm laborVision changes during pregnancy7 Skin Care Tips to Follow During PregnancySystemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) In Pregnancy5 Ways To Cope Up With Back Pain During PregnancyPregnant Women NutritionCorona Virus and PregnancyIntra-uterine contraceptive devices (IUD)Childbirth and NewbornChildbirth - Ways to relief pain during childbirthPreparations For DeliveryInstructions after deliveryPostnatal Exercises - Exercises after deliveryNewborn characteristicsNursing Your Baby - Newborn CareStages of infant development - Baby Development StagesEpidural Analgesia5 Science-Backed Up Benefits Of Breastfeeding Over Formula FeedingPlan for Perfect Babys Feeding ScheduleDepression in Women and Postpartum DepressionGynaecologyGynecological Disorders and DiseasesFemale Reproductive SystemMale Reproductive SystemLinks to Various Articles in Gynaecology and ObstetricsUrinary IncontinenceOvarian CystsCauses for loss of female libido and ways to make it betterEndometriosisUterine FibroidsIntra-uterine contraceptive devices (IUD)Mullerian Ducts Anomalies - Uterine AbnormalitiesMenopause - Hormone Replacement Therapy (hrt)Cloning Humans Myth or Fact Options and ApplicationsHysterectomy - Surgical Removal of the Uterus or wombLabiaplasty - Plastic Surgery of the Female Genital OrgansWeight Loss Supplements for WomenGenital Area Hygiene - Vulvar and Vaginal HygieneDiagnosis and Prevention of Cervical CancerThe Vagina - Vaginal Discharge - Vaginal infectionBreast enlargement - Breast AugmentationG spot – Amplification of the G spotQuestions Related to sexual TopicsContraceptionPolycystic ovariesWhat you should do before and after surgeryPremenstrual syndrome (PMS) Videos about the Reproductive systemPostmenopausal BleedingPlasma injection for urinary incontinencePelvic inflammatory disease (PID)Sexual attraction and attractiveness to othersChronic pelvic pain Lightening Dark Skin around Pubic AreaWound Care After Surgery6 Wellness Things Women Over 40 should be Wary ofLaparoscopy & HysteroscopyLaparoscopy Surgery - Gynecological LaparoscopyLaparoscopy PhotosLaparoscopy Photos 1Laparoscopy Photos 2Laparoscopy Photos 3Laparoscopy Photos 4Laparoscopy Operations VideosHysteroscopy - Hysteroscopy for InfertilityHysteroscopy PhotosHysteroscopy VideosWhat you should do before and after surgeryUltrasound ScanLinks to ultrasound Photos Slide Show 3D 4D Ultrasound Scans PhotosFetal Face Ultrasound Photos3D Fetal Profile Ultrasound Scan PhotosFace Photos Before and After DeliveryFetal Parts Ultrasound Scan Photos3D Fetal Limbs Ultrasound Scan PhotosFirst Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Behavior Ultrasound PhotosMultiple Pregnancy Ultrasound PhotosSecond Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Skeleton Ultrasound Photos4D Ultrasound Scan Fetal Video Clips3D Ultrasound Scan photosAbdominal and General Ultrasound Photos3D Ultrasound Scan Photos gallbladder liver kidney spleen3D Ultrasound Scan intestine urinary bladder thyroid gland and the
stomachPregnancy 3D Ultrasound Scan Photos For ObstetriciansGynecology Ultrasound PhotosGynecology Ultrasound Photos 1Gynecology Ultrasound Photos 2Scrotal - testicular Ultrasound Scan PhotosBreast Ultrasound Scan PhotosThe Clinical Advantages of 3D and 4D UltrasoundQuestions Related To Four Dimensional UltrasoundDefinition and Features of Four Dimensional UltrasoundUses of 4D Ultrasound scanA short History of the development of Ultrasound in Obstetrics and Gynecology Dr. Joseph WooFetal behavior during pregnancyStart Your Baby's Photo AlbumVideo & PhotosVideo Clips4D Ultrasound Scan Fetal Video ClipsVideo clips of the IVF and ICSI proceduresHysteroscopy Video clipsLaparoscopy Video clipsPregnancy Video clipsJordan Video clipsThe construction of the WebsiteThe Internet For the Medical DoctorDr. Najeeb Layyous interview with Jordan TVDr. Najeeb Layyous Interview with Qatar TVVideos about the Reproductive systemPhotos IVF and ICSI PhotosHysteroscopy PhotosLaparoscopy Photos 1Laparoscopy Photos 2Laparoscopy Photos 3Laparoscopy Photos 4Fetal Face Ultrasound Photos3D Fetal Profile Ultrasound Scan PhotosFetal Parts Ultrasound Scan Photos3D Fetal Limbs Ultrasound Scan PhotosFirst Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Behavior Ultrasound PhotosMultiple Pregnancy Ultrasound PhotosSecond Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Skeleton Ultrasound PhotosPregnancy Ultrasound Photos For ObstetriciansAbout JordanJordan HospitalsTravel AgenciesTourist places in JordanJordan UniversityJordan Facts & FiguresMuseums and Galleries in JordanEmergency Calls in JordanAirlines Offices in Jordan Diplomatic Missions in JordanInternational Dialing CodesMinistries of JordanReal Estate Agencies in JordanBanks in JordanSelected Restaurants in Jordan Car Rental in JordanCultural Centers in JordanHotels in JordanJordan LinksJordan Video clipsJordan MapsJordan Photos
Layyous.com
Amman - Jordan
We look after you, and bring Happiness to your life
HomeAssisted ReproductionThe use of PRP (Platelets Rich Plasma) to increase success rate in IVFAssisted Reproductive Technology (ART)In Vitro Fertilization - I.V.FIntracytoplasmic Sperm Injection - ICSIIVF Related Procedures - Cryopreservation - Ovarian hyper stimulation syndrome - OHSSIntra Uterine Insemination - IUI IVF Success Rates - IUI Success RatesIVF And ICSI Videos - Procedure And Process Involved IVF and ICSI PhotosIntracytoplasmic morphologically selected sperm Injection IMSIEmbryo glueAssisted HatchingEmbryo Blastocyst CultureIVF Failure - Treating Failed In Vitro FertilizationPreimplantation Genetic DiagnosisIn Vitro Fertilization Patients Frequently Asked QuestionsFertilized Oocytes and Embryos PhotosIVF Laboratory TourOocytes and Sperms PhotosPhysiological Selection of sperm for ICSI (PICSI)Microsurgical Sperm Retrieval from the Testicle (Micro-TESE)The ART of In vitro Fertilization How to increase fertility for Men And Women for natural concepton and IVFSex selection Before PregnancyInfertilityInfertility GuideFertilization - Fertility PotentialCauses of Infertility in WomenCauses of Infertility in MenDiagnosis Of Infertility In WomenDiagnosis of Infertility In MenTreatment of infertilityHow to increase fertility for Men And Women for natural concepton and IVF Facts About Smoking and FertilityVaricocele Effect on Infertility and its Management Natural Fertility Boosters Herbal supplements For InfertilityPelvic Adhesions And InfertilityStress and InfertilityPolycystic Ovarian Syndrome - PCOSPCO Patients FAQPresent and futuristic developments in fertility treatmentInfertility Frequently Asked QuestionsFrequently Asked QuestionsWeird Factors That Could Affect Your FertilitySleep Correlation with Male InfertilityMale Hypogonadotropic hypogonadismGenetic causes of male infertilityOvarian CystsSex selection Before Pregnancy PregnancyPregnancy GuidePregnancy Month by MonthPregnancy Month by MonthFirst Month Pregnancy - 1 month pregnantSecond Month Pregnancy - 2 months pregnantThird Month Pregnancy - 3 months pregnantFourth-month-pregnancy - 4 months pregnantFifth Month Pregnancy - 5 months pregnantSixth Month Pregnancy - 6 months pregnantSeventh Month Pregnancy - 7 months pregnantEighth Month Pregnancy - 8 months pregnantNinth Month Pregnancy - 9 months pregnantAdvice for Pregnant Women - Tips For Pregnant WomenHeartburn during pregnancySex selection Before PregnancyGestational Diabetes (Diabetes During Pregnancy)Cerebral Palsy Causes Classification and TreatmentCord blood,Umbilical Cord blood CollectionEctopic PregnancyContraception - Different Birth ControlsPiles - Haemorrhoids in PregnancyCauses of Recurrent MiscarriageConstipation During PregnancySex during pregnancyAnemia in pregnancyPregnancy ExercisesPregnancy After 35Pregnancy Video clips7 Most Common Toxins During Pregnancy that Affect your Childs Health and
How To Avoid ThemAnterior Placenta During Pregnancy - Everything You Need to KnowOral Health Care During Pregnancy
| Dr N LayyousPost Pregnancy DietMolar Pregnancy5 Tasty breakfast recipes that will quash your pregnancy blues detectable cravings every dayPreterm laborVision changes during pregnancy7 Skin Care Tips to Follow During PregnancySystemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) In Pregnancy5 Ways To Cope Up With Back Pain During PregnancyPregnant Women NutritionCorona Virus and PregnancyIntra-uterine contraceptive devices (IUD)Childbirth and NewbornChildbirth - Ways to relief pain during childbirthPreparations For DeliveryInstructions after deliveryPostnatal Exercises - Exercises after deliveryNewborn characteristicsNursing Your Baby - Newborn CareStages of infant development - Baby Development StagesEpidural Analgesia5 Science-Backed Up Benefits Of Breastfeeding Over Formula FeedingPlan for Perfect Babys Feeding ScheduleDepression in Women and Postpartum DepressionGynaecologyGynecological Disorders and DiseasesFemale Reproductive SystemMale Reproductive SystemLinks to Various Articles in Gynaecology and ObstetricsUrinary IncontinenceOvarian CystsCauses for loss of female libido and ways to make it betterEndometriosisUterine FibroidsIntra-uterine contraceptive devices (IUD)Mullerian Ducts Anomalies - Uterine AbnormalitiesMenopause - Hormone Replacement Therapy (hrt)Cloning Humans Myth or Fact Options and ApplicationsHysterectomy - Surgical Removal of the Uterus or wombLabiaplasty - Plastic Surgery of the Female Genital OrgansWeight Loss Supplements for WomenGenital Area Hygiene - Vulvar and Vaginal HygieneDiagnosis and Prevention of Cervical CancerThe Vagina - Vaginal Discharge - Vaginal infectionBreast enlargement - Breast AugmentationG spot – Amplification of the G spotQuestions Related to sexual TopicsContraceptionPolycystic ovariesWhat you should do before and after surgeryPremenstrual syndrome (PMS) Videos about the Reproductive systemPostmenopausal BleedingPlasma injection for urinary incontinencePelvic inflammatory disease (PID)Sexual attraction and attractiveness to othersChronic pelvic pain Lightening Dark Skin around Pubic AreaWound Care After Surgery6 Wellness Things Women Over 40 should be Wary ofLaparoscopy & HysteroscopyLaparoscopy Surgery - Gynecological LaparoscopyLaparoscopy PhotosLaparoscopy Photos 1Laparoscopy Photos 2Laparoscopy Photos 3Laparoscopy Photos 4Laparoscopy Operations VideosHysteroscopy - Hysteroscopy for InfertilityHysteroscopy PhotosHysteroscopy VideosWhat you should do before and after surgeryUltrasound ScanLinks to ultrasound Photos Slide Show 3D 4D Ultrasound Scans PhotosFetal Face Ultrasound Photos3D Fetal Profile Ultrasound Scan PhotosFace Photos Before and After DeliveryFetal Parts Ultrasound Scan Photos3D Fetal Limbs Ultrasound Scan PhotosFirst Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Behavior Ultrasound PhotosMultiple Pregnancy Ultrasound PhotosSecond Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Skeleton Ultrasound Photos4D Ultrasound Scan Fetal Video Clips3D Ultrasound Scan photosAbdominal and General Ultrasound Photos3D Ultrasound Scan Photos gallbladder liver kidney spleen3D Ultrasound Scan intestine urinary bladder thyroid gland and the
stomachPregnancy 3D Ultrasound Scan Photos For ObstetriciansGynecology Ultrasound PhotosGynecology Ultrasound Photos 1Gynecology Ultrasound Photos 2Scrotal - testicular Ultrasound Scan PhotosBreast Ultrasound Scan PhotosThe Clinical Advantages of 3D and 4D UltrasoundQuestions Related To Four Dimensional UltrasoundDefinition and Features of Four Dimensional UltrasoundUses of 4D Ultrasound scanA short History of the development of Ultrasound in Obstetrics and Gynecology Dr. Joseph WooFetal behavior during pregnancyStart Your Baby's Photo AlbumVideo & PhotosVideo Clips4D Ultrasound Scan Fetal Video ClipsVideo clips of the IVF and ICSI proceduresHysteroscopy Video clipsLaparoscopy Video clipsPregnancy Video clipsJordan Video clipsThe construction of the WebsiteThe Internet For the Medical DoctorDr. Najeeb Layyous interview with Jordan TVDr. Najeeb Layyous Interview with Qatar TVVideos about the Reproductive systemPhotos IVF and ICSI PhotosHysteroscopy PhotosLaparoscopy Photos 1Laparoscopy Photos 2Laparoscopy Photos 3Laparoscopy Photos 4Fetal Face Ultrasound Photos3D Fetal Profile Ultrasound Scan PhotosFetal Parts Ultrasound Scan Photos3D Fetal Limbs Ultrasound Scan PhotosFirst Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Behavior Ultrasound PhotosMultiple Pregnancy Ultrasound PhotosSecond Trimester Ultrasound PhotosFetal Skeleton Ultrasound PhotosPregnancy Ultrasound Photos For ObstetriciansSite Forums And Live ChatLatest NewsInfertility Health and Medical NewsMedical Health Articles Magazines and ResearchesLatest World NewsCorona Virus ProphylaxisCorona Viruses Disease Website RelatedSitemapRSSPrivacy StatementWebsite Feedback FormAdvertising policyGeneral Website DisclaimerMedical Search and Information PageEnable JavaScript Link to usLink policyThe construction of the WebsiteAbout JordanJordan HospitalsTravel AgenciesTourist places in JordanJordan UniversityJordan Facts & FiguresMuseums and Galleries in JordanEmergency Calls in JordanAirlines Offices in Jordan Diplomatic Missions in JordanInternational Dialing CodesMinistries of JordanReal Estate Agencies in JordanBanks in JordanSelected Restaurants in Jordan Car Rental in JordanCultural Centers in JordanHotels in JordanJordan LinksJordan Video clipsJordan MapsJordan PhotosDr. Najeeb LayyousAbout Dr. Najeeb LayyousLocation Of Dr. Najeeb Layyous CenterVisit Our Center And Available treatmentsGynaecological-Infertility free Consultation Contact Dr Najeeb Layyous Center Website AwardsMusic To Enjoy
Latest
The ART of In vitro Fertilization
Corona Virus and Pregnancy
Corona Viruses Disease
Corona Virus Prophylaxis
Forums
Pregnancy Due Date Calculator
Chinese Gender Predictor
Our Commitment to Privacy
Dr Najeeb Layyous is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy as a visitor to his Web site at http://www.layyous.com. We take the issue of privacy very seriously and value the trust you place in us each time you use our services and access this Web site. This Privacy Statement describes the practices and policies we have put into place to safeguard your personal and health-related personal information that may be gathered and used as you visit our Web site.
THIS NOTICE DESCRIBES HOW MEDICAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAY BE USED AND DISCLOSED AND HOW YOU CAN GET ACCESS TO THIS INFORMATION. PLEASE REVIEW IT CAREFULL.
The policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, we encourage you to contact us using any of the methods outlined at the end of our Privacy Statement.
Who Is Collecting the Information?
Dr Najeeb Layyous is collecting information on this Web site as outlined in this privacy statement.
What Information Do We Collect? and how do we use it?
Automatic Collection of Information:
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site or download information, our system will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and is used in an aggregate way to help us improve our web site and tell us the number of visitors to our site each day.
Permission-based Collection of Information:
At different places on our site depending upon the feature you use, you may be asked to volunteer personal and health-related information such as your name, email, mailing address, telephone number, and health history.
With Whom Will the Information Be Shared?
The personally identifiable information gathered during your visit to this Web site is not shared with any organization for any purpose.
Dr Najeeb Layyous has the right to reveal the personally, identifiable information for website visitors in cases which involves legal issues to defend himself and his website or a user of the website.
Access and Correction of Personal Information
Review of Personal Information
Site visitors may not access information we have collected and maintain about them
Use of our forum and other public places in our website.
Dr Najeeb Layyous site contains infertility and endoscopey public forum. the information submitted in this forum is public and its privacy cannot be controlled . so any information that you submit in the forum is public and you are warned not to submit private information.
Our Use of Cookies
We do not use any cookies to store or collect information on our Web site.
Registration for Access
Visitors can use this entire Web site anonymously, without registration.
Family safe site
We are especially concerned about protecting children's privacy. We hope parents and teachers are involved in children's Internet explorations. It is particularly important for parents to guide their children when children are asked to provide personal information on line.
Dr Najeeb Layyous site is an educational site containing information about infertility, male and female genital system's anatomy and information about pregnancy and delivery, which are within the limits put in any educational school program . however Dr Najeeb Layyous stresses that it is up to the parents to decide which age group from their family is allowed to visit his site, as concepts and beliefs vary amongst different families.
Security of Communications
We recognize that many people are concerned about the privacy and protection of information as it is transmitted over the Internet. You should keep in mind that the possibility exists for unauthorized individuals to intercept any email message you send over the Internet.
We use e-mail forms and consultation forms to allow our visitors to ask questions about our services, available treatments and ask for free consultation. These are not hosted on a secure server. The possibility exists that unauthorized individuals may intercept email messages.
E-commerce and On-line Donations
Purchasing items or making donations over the Internet usually requires you to provide your personal identifying information and credit card information on a Web site. Many people have become accustomed to on-line commerce as a time-saving and useful convenience. There are a number of practices that can make providing your sensitive credit card information more secure and therefore make you feel more comfortable about doing so.
At this time, we do not process credit card payments for donations, or advertising on our Web site.
Advertising Servers
On-line advertising, such as banner ads, has become commonplace on many Web sites. Certain Web sites have developed relationships with third-party advertising servers to display these advertisements on their sites. By clicking on one of these banner ads, you will be taken to another site with different privacy policies. These third party ad servers may also use cookies to collect non-personal information on your preferences and interests via the advertisement you decide to view.
we encourage users to review the privacy policy of each advertising company as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these sites.
Links to Other Sites
Web sites often provide a number of links that offer direct access to other useful or interesting web sites holding potential value to site visitors. Inclusion of the other sites by links does not imply any endorsement of the material or information on the other sites. Users are encouraged to review the privacy policy of each linked site before sharing personal and health-related information.
This site includes links to non-affiliated external Web sites. We have the following practices:
We encourage users to review the privacy policy of each linked site, as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.
Changes in Our Privacy Policy
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we  will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Web Site Contact Information
If you have questions about our privacy policy, or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us.
Contact: Dr Najeeb Layyous F.R.C.O.G
Tel: clinic    96265656575
Fax: 96265655293
P.O.Box 830038,Amman 11183,Jordan
e-mail: layyous@layyous.com
www.layyous.com
Modification Date
This privacy statement was last modified on September 4, 2003.
Dr Najeeb Layyous  F.R.C.O.G
Consultant Obstetrician, Gynecologist and Infertility Specialist
Last Update: 2019-10-17
Advertisement
Advertisement
See Also :
Sitemap
RSS
Privacy Statement
Website Feedback Form
Advertising policy
General Website Disclaimer
Medical Search and Information Page
Enable JavaScript
Advertisement
Browse Layyous.com Website:
Website RelatedSitemapRSSPrivacy StatementWebsite Feedback FormAdvertising policyGeneral Website DisclaimerMedical Search and Information PageEnable JavaScript Link to usLink policyThe construction of the WebsiteDr. Najeeb LayyousAbout Dr. Najeeb LayyousLocation Of Dr. Najeeb Layyous CenterVisit Our Center And Available treatmentsGynaecological-Infertility free Consultation Contact Dr Najeeb Layyous Center Website Awards
Contact Info
Telephone : +962 6 5656575
Fax
: +962 6 5655293
E - mail: layyous@layyous.com
P.O. Box: 830038 Amman - Jordan 11183
All data at this web site are copyright © Sponsored by Dr. Najeeb Layyous, P.O Box 830038 Zahran Post Office 11183 Amman-Jordan, All rights reserved. powered by Arak.
